(Leonard:)Because I don't
need his girlfriend
(Leonard:)to set me up with one
of her girlfriends.
(Leonard:)I'm perfectly capable of
finding a girl on my own.
(Raj:)Oh, Leonard, you remind me
(Raj:)of the funny old story
about a man
(Raj:)who walks into a women's
correctional institution
(Raj:)with a stack of paperwork
(Raj:)that will allow
the female convicts to go free.
(Leonard:)You're saying I
couldn't get laid
(Leonard:)in a women's prison with
a handful of pardons.
(Raj:)Are you going to let me
tell the story or not?
(Sheldon:)Leonard?
(Sheldon:)Are you sleeping?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Sheldon:)Are you ill?
(Sheldon:)Are you still depressed
(Sheldon:)because you're alone,
and no one loves you?
(Leonard:)I don't know. Maybe.
(Sheldon:)I want you to know
that I'm genuinely concerned
(Sheldon:)about your well-being.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
You're welcome.
(Sheldon:)But it's still no reason
to have your feet in my spot.
(Amy(on webcam):)May I offer an observation?
(Leonard:)What the hell?
How long has she been here?